Paras R. Panchal



Dot Net Developer

R No 11, Priyadarshini Bldg, Kisan Nagar No:1, Wagle Estate, Thane 400604

https://github.com/paras245

aparaspanchal5555@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/paras-panchal-718679223

9867556078

Date Of Birth:01-06-2001

PROFILE SUMMARY

Junior Dot Net Web Developer

Web developer with 1 year and 6 months of experience using .NET and .NET Core technologies also worked on Angular. Proficient in C#, object-oriented programming, and web development principles. Eager to learn and contribute to a team environment.

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

OOPS Principle .Net FrameWork

.Net Core Swagger Minimal API

Web API LINQ

MVC Pattern Dapper ORM

C# MSSQL

Angular HTML CSS and Basic JavaScript

Git

OTHER SKILLS

Good Communication & Management Skill

Good at Presentation Skill

Knowledge on ERP System

Research Paper Writing

Creative Thinker

Al prompting

Belief in Team Work and Ability to Adapt.

Ability to Work On PAN and International level.

Always Giving the best and keen to learn new things and responsible for the overall betterment and contributing as much as possible.

QUALIFICATION

Satish Pradhan Dnyanasadhana College

Course: Bsc Computer Science

Over All CGPI: 7.92

TYCS: 5th Sem: Grade A 6th Sem: Grade A

SYCS : 3rd Sem : Grade O 4th Sem : Grade O

FYCS : 1st Sem : Grade B 2nd Sem : Grade B+

K.J Somaiya College Of Science (2018-2019)

H.S.C Percentage:55.85%

Navodaya English High School (2016-2017)

SSC Percentage: 77.20%

WORK EXPERIENCE

Year:2022 - 23

Sushma Technology Private Limited

Took an Internship of 3 months and worked as a Junior Software Developer from June 2022 till Feb 2023. Over this period, I gained knowledge on MVC pattern and worked on ERP Projects for LIPL(LIZMONTAGENS INDIA PVT. LTD), FBIPL (Appraisal System), Pragati (Material Management System) and FBIPL Dossier (Medical Dosage and Document System) here I gained knowledge on basic working of ERP systems and became know to C# Development.

Location: Mumbai

Location: Ahemdabad

Year:2023 - 24(Present)

TechnoBrains Business Solutions

Gained PAN Experience .Took Training For 3 months From March to June on a .Net Core Development For Backend and Angular a bit for Frontend along with other web technology. Here I gained my most knowledge about coding and Development and started working as a Junior Software Developer on Precise RadFlow 360 a (US Medical Project) and I am working currently in this company from March to untill Present.

RESPONSIBILITY

- Develop new features and functionalities for existing .NET Core applications.
- Implement bug fixes and improve code quality.
- Write and Perform unit tests for assigned API.
- Participate in code reviews and contribute to team discussions.
- Communicate effectively with other developers, testers
- Seek help and clarification when needed, and actively learn from senior developers.

PROJECTS

- Made a Simple Invoice Management System using .Net Core MVC Pattern.
- Angular Project based on Employee CRUD using .Net Core API in BackEnd.
- Worked on API on some new Features for .Net Core.
- A simple website Using TailWind CSS.